{
    "id": "29_Society_87",
    "claim": ", an initiative that offers us a tool to confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies. The development of technology leads humans to have advantages and disadvantages in relatively short time, we have moved from the control of information through official lies in the media and rumors that were running slowly in society at the end of the s, to the ease that any 'citizen 'invents his own vision of things, that this news is true, biased or totally false, can be replicated from any mobile phone, having reach in unimaginable people, and that artificial intelligence algorithms are programmed to viralize and expand the reach of those messages. The objective of both situations remains the same, trying to impact society as a whole to modify social routine, of course it also has its advantages, such as achieving a more direct communication without intermediaries, but there is a degree of social paroxysm that generated reaching the concept of 'false news ', which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty, suddenly these realities began to be a daily matter. Fortunately for us in Mexico, last week the initiative called Verificado was born. mx , led by the digital newspaper Animal Pol√≠tica, in conjunction with universities and civil society organizations and more than  media, which will be given the task of being for the next four months, the flow of news to determine if they are false or not. This initiative has been in operation for more than a week and on its page you can already find a lot of denials to news that had gone viral as real news, today citizens should start our day by reviewing that it is false or not, before beginning to watch the news, in order to discard the false news of the previous days, entering the verified page. mx we can realize that the flows of false lies are huge and that the election campaigns are not yet beginning, imagine that for every candidate that is in contention there will be at least three or four opponents who will be inventing lies, this will be added to the three levels of government where people will be elected and will be able to imagine the amount of lies that will flood us. This system, through different technological tools, detects the news that goes viral at an unusual speed and reviews them, but also offers citizens the option to request the verification of a news item by tagging the news in question on Twitter with the hashtag: #I WanttoVerify. The verification action is a titanic work by the group created by this collective, but little by little the denials of the news that are impacting Mexican society the fastest begin to flow. Information and tools are now available, and citizens in a responsible and informed attitude need to consult and contribute to its use. This exercise is going to have a very powerful effect on the system of political, electoral communication and on the practice of the media and citizens. Today, a stream of denials is being created for false news. If we use it correctly, we can improve the information and the way we communicate with politicians, as it will be more difficult to tell lies in the media or in speeches. An example of how you can use this initiative happened to me last week in a chat of friends on WhatsApp, where all the participants before each meme immediately get disgusted in comments, one day someone put one of those fake news and the moment I read it, went to the verification and sent them the lie, the result was very curious and I sum it up as the famous phrase of the song'Ella 'by Jose Alfredo Jimenez, in the chat, 'the mariachis silenced'. Let's realize that each of us reporting correctly and not viralizing things that aren't verified can improve the flow of true information. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.forbes.com.mx",
    "date": "21/03/2018",
    "veracity": 1,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "This initiative an initiative that offers us a tool to confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies This initiative an initiative that offers us a tool to confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is this initiative?",
                    "answer": "an initiative that offers us a tool to confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the initiative offer us a tool to combat the flow of false news?",
                    "score": 0.8311,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThis|det\tan|det\tthat|nsubj\tus|dative\ta|det\tto|aux\tthe|det\tfalse|amod\tfalse news|pobj\tthat|nsubjpass\tis|aux\tbeing|auxpass\tthe|det\tsocial|amod\tto|aux\tlies|dobj\tThis|det\tan|det\tthat|nsubj\tus|dative\ta|det\tto|aux\tthe|det\tfalse|amod\tthat|nsubjpass\tis|aux\tbeing|auxpass\tthe|det\tsocial|amod\tto|aux\tlies|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the use of social networks to create false news?",
                    "score": 0.7969,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx|nsubj\ton 21/03/2018|prep\tthat is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies|relcl\tby the ease of social networks to invent lies|agent\tthe ease of social networks to invent lies|pobj\tsocial networks|pobj\tto invent lies|acl\tof false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies|prep\tfalse news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies|pobj\tthat is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies|relcl\tby the ease of social networks to invent lies|agent\tthe ease of social networks to invent lies|pobj\tsocial networks|pobj\tto invent lies|acl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The development of citizens leads humans to have advantages and disadvantages in relatively short time, we have moved from the control of information through official lies in the media and rumors that were running slowly in society at the end of the s, to the ease that any 'citizen ' invents own vision of things, that this news is true, biased or totally false, can be replicated from any mobile phone, having reach in unimaginable people, and that artificial intelligence algorithms are programmed to viralize and expand the reach of those messages.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is it called when a person invents their own vision of things?",
                    "answer": "'citizen"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does artificial intelligence algorithms do to expand the reach of messages?",
                    "score": 0.7763,
                    "answers": "expand the reach of those messages|conj\tthose messages|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the advantages and disadvantages of artificial intelligence algorithms?",
                    "score": 0.7275,
                    "answers": "artificial intelligence algorithms|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the technology that can be replicated from any mobile phone?",
                    "score": 0.6905,
                    "answers": "the ease that any ' citizen ' invents own vision of things , that this news is true , biased or totally false , can be replicated from any mobile phone , having reach in unimaginable people , and that artificial intelligence algorithms are programmed to viralize and expand the reach of those messages|pobj\tthat this news is true , biased or totally false , can be replicated from any mobile phone , having reach in unimaginable people , and that artificial intelligence algorithms are programmed to viralize and expand the reach of those messages|conj\tcan be replicated from any mobile phone , having reach in unimaginable people|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the information that humans receive from the government?",
                    "score": 0.6873,
                    "answers": "rumors|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is artificial intelligence?",
                    "score": 0.652,
                    "answers": "artificial|amod\tartificial intelligence|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The objective of both situations remains This initiative , trying to impact society as a whole to modify social the news that goes viral at an unusual speed , such the news that goes viral at an unusual speed achieving a more direct communication without intermediaries, but there a news item of social a news item reaching the concept of 'false news ', which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty , suddenly these Information and tools be a daily matter.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the objective of both situations?",
                    "answer": "This initiative"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of creating fake news?",
                    "score": 0.6729,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx reported on 21/03/2018 that The objective of both situations remains This initiative , trying to impact society as a whole to modify social the news that goes viral at an unusual speed , such the news that goes viral at an unusual speed achieving a more direct communication without intermediaries , but there a news item of social a news item reaching the concept of ' false news ' , which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty , suddenly these Information and tools be a daily matter|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are false news?",
                    "score": 0.6567,
                    "answers": "of ' false news ' , which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|prep\t' false news ' , which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is false news?",
                    "score": 0.645,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx|nsubj\ton 21/03/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tThe objective of both situations|nsubj\tof both situations|prep\tboth|det\tboth situations|pobj\tThis|det\t,|punct\tto|aux\tsociety as a whole|dobj\tas a whole|prep\ta|det\ta whole|pobj\tto|aux\tsocial|dobj\tthe|det\tthe news that goes viral at an unusual speed , such the news that goes viral at an unusual speed achieving a more direct communication without intermediaries|dobj\tthat|nsubj\tthat goes viral at an unusual speed|relcl\tviral|acomp\tat an unusual speed|prep\tan|det\tunusual|amod\tan unusual speed|pobj\t,|punct\tsuch|predet\tthe|det\tsuch the news that goes viral at an unusual speed achieving a more direct communication without intermediaries|appos\tthat|nsubj\tviral|acomp\tat an unusual speed|prep\tan|det\tunusual|amod\tan unusual speed|pobj\ta|det\tmore|advmod\tmore direct|amod\twithout intermediaries|prep\tintermediaries|pobj\t,|punct\tbut|cc\tthere|expl\ta|det\tnews|compound\ta news item of social a news item reaching the concept of ' false news ' , which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|dep\tof social|prep\tsocial|pobj\ta|det\tnews|compound\ta news item reaching the concept of ' false news ' , which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|appos\treaching the concept of ' false news ' , which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|acl\tthe|det\tthe concept of ' false news ' , which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|dobj\t'|punct\tfalse|amod\t'|punct\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|relcl\tstories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|attr\tand|cc\tcontents|conj\twith unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|prep\tunverified|amod\tunverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|pobj\tthat|nsubj\tthat runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|relcl\tthrough social networks|prep\tsocial|amod\tsocial networks|pobj\tand|cc\tthat|mark\tpeople|nsubj\tthat people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty|conj\tthem|dobj\tas real information|prep\treal|amod\treal information|pobj\tcausing disinformation and uncertainty|advcl\tdisinformation and uncertainty|dobj\tand|cc\tuncertainty|conj\t,|punct\tsuddenly|advmod\tthese|det\tthese Information and tools|nsubj\tand|cc\ttools|conj\tthere a news item of social a news item reaching the concept of ' false news ' , which are stories and contents with unverified information that runs through social networks and that people take them as real information causing disinformation and uncertainty , suddenly these Information and tools be a daily matter|conj\ta|det\tdaily|amod\ta daily matter|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Fortunately for us in Mexico, last week an initiative that offers us a tool to confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies was born.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the initiative that was created by forbes?",
                    "answer": "an initiative that offers us a tool to confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the flow of false news that is being generated by social networks to invent lies?",
                    "score": 0.7257,
                    "answers": "us in Mexico|pobj\tthe flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies|dobj\tof false news|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the use of social networks to create false news?",
                    "score": 0.6966,
                    "answers": "on 21/03/2018|prep\tan initiative that offers us a tool to confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies|nsubjpass\tthat offers us a tool to confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies|relcl\tto confront the flow of false news that is being generated by the ease of social networks to invent lies|relcl\tby the ease of social networks to invent lies|agent\tthe ease of social networks to invent lies|pobj\tof social networks|prep\tsocial|amod\tsocial networks|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "mx , Information and tools by the digital newspaper Animal Pol√≠tica, in conjunction with universities and civil society organizations and more than  media, which will be given the task of being for the next four months, the flow of news to determine if news are false or not.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 21/03/2018 that mx, Information and tools by the digital newspaper Animal Poltica, in conjunction with universities and civil society organizations and more than media?",
                    "answer": "mx"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the digital newspaper Animal Pol√≠tica and universities and civil society organizations?",
                    "score": 0.5488,
                    "answers": "conjunction with universities and civil society organizations and more than|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Animal Pol√≠tica?",
                    "score": 0.5158,
                    "answers": ",|punct\tby the digital newspaper Animal Pol√≠tica ,|prep\tdigital|amod\tAnimal|compound\t,|punct\tmore than|conj\t,|punct\tfour|nummod\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the flow of news to determine if news is false or not?",
                    "score": 0.4976,
                    "answers": "that mx , Information and tools by the digital newspaper Animal Pol√≠tica , in conjunction with universities and civil society organizations and more than   media , which will be given the task of being for the next four months , the flow of news to determine if news are false or not|dobj\tthan|prep\twhich will be given the task of being for the next four months , the flow of news to determine if news are false or not|relcl\tnews|pobj\tto determine if news are false or not|advcl\tnews|nsubj\tfalse|acomp\tnot|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the news that is false or not real?",
                    "score": 0.4783,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tand|cc\tthe|det\tand|cc\tand|cc\twhich|nsubjpass\twill|aux\tthe|det\tthe|det\tnext|amod\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This initiative has been in operation for more than a week and on its page you can already find a lot of denials to news that had gone viral as real news, today citizens should start our day by reviewing that it is false or not, before beginning to watch the news, in order to discard the false news of the previous days, entering the verified page.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How long has the Forbes initiative been in operation?",
                    "answer": "more than a week"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many denials have gone viral as real news?",
                    "score": 0.7033,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThis|det\tThis initiative|nsubj\thas|aux\tin operation|prep\toperation|pobj\tmore|amod\tthan|quantmod\tmore than a|nummod\tand|cc\ton its page|prep\tits|poss\tits page|pobj\tyou|nsubj\tcan|aux\talready|advmod\ton its page you can already find a lot of denials to news that had gone viral as real news|conj\ta|det\ta lot of denials to news that had gone viral as real news|dobj\tthat|nsubj\thad|aux\tviral|acomp\treal|amod\t,|punct\tcitizens|nsubj\tour|poss\tthat|mark\tit|nsubj\tor|cc\t,|punct\tto|aux\tthe|det\tthe news|dobj\t,|punct\tto|aux\tthe|det\tof the previous days|prep\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long has it been since this initiative has been in operation?",
                    "score": 0.6733,
                    "answers": "that This initiative has been in operation for more than a week|ccomp\tfor more than a week|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the denials to news that went viral?",
                    "score": 0.6522,
                    "answers": "to news that had gone viral as real news|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many denials are there each week?",
                    "score": 0.6334,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx reported on 21/03/2018 that This initiative has been in operation for more than a week and on its page you can already find a lot of denials to news that had gone viral as real news|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process used to discard false news?",
                    "score": 0.6097,
                    "answers": "in order to discard the false news of the previous days|prep\torder to discard the false news of the previous days|pobj\tto discard the false news of the previous days|acl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "mx we can realize that the flows of false lies are huge and that the election campaigns are not yet beginning, imagine that for every candidate that is in contention there will be at least three or four opponents who will be inventing lies, this will be added to the three levels of government where people will be elected and will be able to imagine the amount of lies that will flood us.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many opponents will be inventing lies for every candidate that is in contention?",
                    "answer": "at least three or four"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the flows of false lies in the 2018 election campaigns?",
                    "score": 0.6591,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many opponents will be in contention for the 2018 election?",
                    "score": 0.6377,
                    "answers": "for every candidate that is in contention|prep\tevery candidate that is in contention|pobj\tthat is in contention|relcl\tin contention|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people will be elected in the 2018 election?",
                    "score": 0.6128,
                    "answers": "at least|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the spread of false lies?",
                    "score": 0.5954,
                    "answers": "mx we can realize that the flows of false lies are huge and that the election campaigns are not yet beginning|ccomp\tof false lies|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the amount of false lies that are being spread?",
                    "score": 0.5922,
                    "answers": "that the flows of false lies are huge and that the election campaigns are not yet beginning|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This system, through different technological tools, detects the news that goes viral at an unusual speed and reviews them, but also offers citizens the option to request the verification of a news item by tagging the news in question on Twitter with the hashtag: #I WanttoVerify.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what platform can citizens request verification of a news item by tagging it with the hashtag: #I WanttoVerify?",
                    "answer": "Twitter"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Can citizens request the verification of a news item on Twitter?",
                    "score": 0.7748,
                    "answers": "also offers citizens the option to request the verification of a news item by tagging the news in question on Twitter with the hashtag : # I WanttoVerify|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the technology used to detect a news item?",
                    "score": 0.6851,
                    "answers": "unusual|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process used to verify news items on Twitter?",
                    "score": 0.682,
                    "answers": "Twitter|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the speed of a news item?",
                    "score": 0.6579,
                    "answers": "an unusual speed|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the #I WanttoVerify?",
                    "score": 0.6133,
                    "answers": "the hashtag : # I WanttoVerify|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The verification action is a titanic work by the group created by this collective, but little by little the denials of the news that are impacting Mexican society the fastest begin to flow.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is impacting Mexican society the fastest?",
                    "answer": "the denials of the news"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are denials of news that are impacting Mexican society the fastest?",
                    "score": 0.843,
                    "answers": "the denials of the news that are impacting Mexican society the fastest|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many denials of news are there each year?",
                    "score": 0.7935,
                    "answers": "this collective|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who created the verification action?",
                    "score": 0.7584,
                    "answers": "by the group created by this collective|prep\tthe group created by this collective|pobj\tcreated by this collective|acl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Information and tools are now available, and citizens in a responsible and informed attitude need to consult and contribute to its use.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who needs to consult and contribute to the use of forbes?",
                    "answer": "citizens in a responsible and informed attitude"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much information and tools are available to citizens?",
                    "score": 0.8733,
                    "answers": "contribute to its use|conj\tto its use|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people need to consult and contribute to the use of technology?",
                    "score": 0.8272,
                    "answers": "citizens in a responsible and informed attitude need to consult and contribute to its use|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the use of the internet?",
                    "score": 0.7062,
                    "answers": "its use|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of the information and tools available?",
                    "score": 0.7047,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx reported on 21/03/2018 that Information and tools are now available , and citizens in a responsible and informed attitude need to consult and contribute to its use|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This exercise is going to have a very powerful effect on the system of political, electoral communication and on the practice of the media and citizens.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did forbes report that this exercise was going to have a very powerful effect on the system of political, electoral communication and on the practice of the media and citizens?",
                    "answer": "21/03/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How will the exercise affect the system of political, electoral communication and practice of the media and citizens?",
                    "score": 0.7526,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx reported on 21/03/2018 that This exercise is going to have a very powerful effect on the system of political , electoral communication and on the practice of the media and citizens|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the exercise?",
                    "score": 0.5887,
                    "answers": "This exercise|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the political system in Africa?",
                    "score": 0.5563,
                    "answers": "political|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Today, a stream of denials is being created for false news.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of news were the denials created for?",
                    "answer": "false news"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the denials that are being created for false news?",
                    "score": 0.8334,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx|nsubj\tthat|mark\t,|punct\tis|aux\tfor false news|prep\tfalse|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are denials?",
                    "score": 0.787,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx reported on 21/03/2018 that Today , a stream of denials is being created for false news|ROOT\ton 21/03/2018|prep\ta|det\ta stream of denials|nsubjpass\tof denials|prep\tdenials|pobj\tbeing|auxpass\tthat Today , a stream of denials is being created for false news|ccomp\tfalse news|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If we use it correctly, we can improve the information and the way we communicate with politicians, as it will be more difficult to tell lies in the media or in speeches.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did forbes say we could improve the way we communicate with politicians?",
                    "answer": "it will be more difficult to tell lies in the media or in speeches"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How can we improve the way we communicate with politicians?",
                    "score": 0.8383,
                    "answers": "that If we use it correctly , we can improve the information and the way we communicate with politicians , as it will be more difficult to tell lies in the media or in speeches|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process used to improve the information and communication with politicians?",
                    "score": 0.7409,
                    "answers": "to tell lies in the media or in speeches|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the best way to improve communication with politicians?",
                    "score": 0.7332,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx reported on 21/03/2018 that If we use it correctly , we can improve the information and the way we communicate with politicians , as it will be more difficult to tell lies in the media or in speeches|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the media?",
                    "score": 0.6669,
                    "answers": "the media|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "An example of how you can use this initiative happened to me last week in a chat of friends on WhatsApp, where all the participants before each meme immediately get disgusted in comments, one day someone put one of those fake news and the moment I read it, went to the verification and sent them the lie, the result was very curious and I sum it up as the famous phrase of the song'Ella 'by Jose Alfredo Jimenez, in the chat, 'the mariachis silenced'.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the song by Jose Alfredo Jimenez?",
                    "answer": "the famous phrase of the song'Ella"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How can you use this initiative?",
                    "score": 0.6609,
                    "answers": "of how you can use this initiative|prep\thow you can use this initiative|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of using fake news on WhatsApp?",
                    "score": 0.6279,
                    "answers": "An example of how you can use this initiative|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of the song Ella by Jose Alfredo Jimenez?",
                    "score": 0.6189,
                    "answers": "Alfredo|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the fake news that you can use on WhatsApp?",
                    "score": 0.612,
                    "answers": "www.forbes.com.mx reported on 21/03/2018 that An example of how you can use this initiative happened to me last week in a chat of friends on WhatsApp , where all the participants before each meme immediately get disgusted in comments , one day someone put one of those fake news and the moment I read it , went to the verification and sent them the lie , the result was very curious and I sum it up as the famous phrase of the song'Ella ' by Jose Alfredo Jimenez , in the chat , ' the mariachis silenced '|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the method used to verify fake news?",
                    "score": 0.6118,
                    "answers": "to the verification|prep\tthe verification|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Let's realize that each of us reporting correctly and not viralizing things that aren't verified can improve the flow of true information.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did forbes report on 21/03/2018?",
                    "answer": "can improve the flow of true information"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How can reporting correctly and not viralizing things that aren't verified improve the flow of true information?",
                    "score": 0.8785,
                    "answers": "can|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of verified information?",
                    "score": 0.7275,
                    "answers": "things that are n't verified|dobj\tthat are n't verified|relcl"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}